The Brink is a documentary film directed by Alison Klayman.
Now unconstrained by an official post, Steve Bannon is free to peddle influence as a
perceived kingmaker, who some say still has a direct line to the White House.
After anointing himself leader of the “populist movement,” he travels around the North
America and Europe spreading his hard-line anti-immigration message.
Self, played by Steve Bannon.
Self, played by Nigel Farage.
Self, played by Sean Bannon.
Self, played by Patrick Caddell.
Self, played by Kent Ekeroth.
Self, played by Daniel Fleuette.
The Brink is a 2019 documentary film, directed by Alison Klayman.
The film is produced by Marie Therese Guirgis, and Alison Klayman under the
banner of AliKlay Productions, Claverie Films, and  RYOT Films.
The film stars Steve Bannon.